Finding Aid for the Pamela Grace Burton papers LSC.2428
UCLA Library Special Collections
Pamela Grace Burton papers
1970-2018
UCLA Library Special Collections
Burton, Pamela, 1948-
Hertz, Richard, 1940-
LSC.2428
108 Linear Feet (99 boxes)
7.5 Linear Feet (7 unprocessed boxes)
855 Gigabytes (11,448 files, 532 Folders) Files transferred from 1 hard drive.
Pamela Burton & Company, an internationally recognized and award-winning landscape architecture firm, has maintained a collection of archives spanning nearly forty-five years of design work. In 1975, Pamela Burton established the company in Santa Monica, California, where the firm has remained ever since. Pamela Burton & Company works in a variety of project typologies and scales, including residential, large-scale residential, commercial, institutional, and municipal. The goal has always been to integrate and harmonize the disciplines of landscape, architecture, and art in a site's cultural and physical environment, while being committed to sustainable design. The archival collection contains both physical and digital material that reveal Pamela Burton & Company's design processes and procedures, project documentation, and firm recognition.
Conditions Governing Access
Portions of collection unprocessed. Unprocessed oversize material is unavailable for access. Please see LSC's Access to Unprocessed Collections Policy for more information about levels of discovery and access of special collections materials and registering interest in unprocessed collections.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS DIGITAL MATERIALS: This collection contains processed digital materials. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9996904111806533
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Pamela Grace Burton and Richard Alan Hertz, 2022.
Biographical History
Pamela Burton & Company, an internationally recognized and award-winning landscape architecture firm, has maintained a collection of archives spanning nearly forty-five years of design work. In 1975, Pamela Burton established the company in Santa Monica, California, where the firm has remained ever since. Pamela Burton & Company works in a variety of project typologies and scales, including residential, large-scale residential, commercial, institutional, and municipal. The goal has always been to integrate and harmonize the disciplines of landscape, architecture, and art in a site's cultural and physical environment, while being committed to sustainable design. Pamela Burton & Company continues to create comprehensive landscape architecture design styles for both private and public spaces around the world.
Scope and Contents
The physical part of the collection includes project rolls of drawings and construction documents; project booklets of presentations and site imagery; project binders of proposals and contracts; slide films of project photography and Pamela Burton's academic research; publications of books and articles about the firm and Pamela Burton; Pamela Burton's project composition notebooks; three-dimensional scale models; and Pamela Burton's personal journals. This collection of hand-drawn and printed material presents all aspects of the firm's projects, from preliminary concepts, revisions, and sketches, to final completion. The work produced over more than four decades displays Pamela Burton's design philosophy and passion, as well as that of all of the team members collectively. The digital portion of the collection is a digitized copy of some of the physical media mentioned above. The digital material includes scans of sketches, diagrams, drawings, construction documents, surveys, and maps. The significant details of most projects have been scanned into the computer as digital files. The wide assortment of material in this collection demonstrate the evolution of landscape architecture design practice, methodology, and technology throughout the years. In particular, from the 1970s to the early 2000s, the collection exemplifies the crucial shift of design work produced by hand into the display of work through computer-aided design.
Women landscape architects; Landscape architecture; Burton, Pamela, 1948-; Hertz, Richard, 1940-
- Project booklets, 1980-2018; 92.6 Linear Feet (65 boxes); 6.6 Linear Feet (5 unprocessed boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  These are 11"x17" bound presentation booklets made as overviews for PB&Co projects. The hand-drawn and/or printed material classified as a booklet can be any of the following: 11"x17" presentation booklets, architectural drawings, construction documents, sketches, plant imagery and information, reference imagery, research, site photographs and documentation, articles, meeting notes, and project correspondence. Some projects have only one booklet, while others have several. The selected project booklets in this archive range from projects beginning in the early 1980s through ones beginning in 2012.
  - Meridien Gardens Hotel, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Lantana, 1996-2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Farmers Market, 2000-2006 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Hard Rock Café Office, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Donum Winery Estate, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - Colorado Center (Yahoo), 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 1-2, Box 4)
  - McMaster-Carr, 2003-2005 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 101, Folder 1)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Unprocessed oversize material is unavailable for access. Please see LSC's Access to Unprocessed Collections Policy for more information about levels of discovery and access of special collections materials and registering interest in unprocessed collections.
  - Aivazovskoje Resort (Black Sea), 2004 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Long Ridge Center, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
  - Cornerstone Sonoma Gallery, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - Bandera Restaurant Dallas, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Icon Brickell, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Treyarch, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Maple Plaza, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Tides Hotel, 2005-2008 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1430 Olympic Boulevard, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 6300 Wilshire, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Ikal del Mar, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Brazil Esplanade, 2006-2009 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Palm Spiral, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Blackwelder Creative Campus (La Cienega), 2007-2008 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Campus at North First, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Rockefeller Center Office Terrace Gardens/Streetscape, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
  - Beckman Coulter, 2007-2010 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 606 Broadway, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Rochavera, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - RPA Jefferson, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - DTS Corporate Headquarters, 2008-2009 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Civic Center Drive, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - KAL H2 (KAL Hyatt), 2011-2013 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Hudson Pacific, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Sony Capra + Sony Rainbow, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Arrowhead Regional Medical Center (San Bernardino Medical Center), 1990-1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Dong Hwa University, 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 2-4)
  - UC Riverside Science Library, 1992-2002 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - High Desert Medical Center, 1993-1998 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - UCSB De La Guerra Dining Commons, 1994-2001 (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
  - University of Redlands Masterplan, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - University of Redlands University Center + Melrose Hall, 1995-1998 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - CSUN Masterplan, 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - University of Redlands Colton Avenue, 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Scripps College East/West Allee, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Horace Mann Children's Charette, 1998-2003 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Mission (Church of the Holy Family), 1998-2011 (Box 15, Folder 3, Box 16, Folder 1-3, Box 17, Box 18, Folder 1-2, Box 92, Folder 1-6, Box 93)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 101, Folder 2-4)
  - SMUCLA Orthopaedic Medical Center, 1998-2012 (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
  - Scripps College Entry Ninth/Columbia, 1999-2002 (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
  - City of Hope Medical Center (Replacement Hospital) Masterplan, 1999-2004 (Box 54, Folder 3, Box 93, Folder 4)
  - UCI Claire Trevor School of the Arts (SOTA) Arts Plaza, 2000-2005 (Box 54, Folder 5, Box 55, Folder 1, Box 93)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - UC Riverside Engineering Building II (RBB), 2001-2005 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - CSU Channel Islands, 2001-2007 (Box 55, Folder 3, Box 56, Folder 1, Box 93, Folder 6)
  - UCSB San Clemente Housing, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 2-3)
  - Webb Schools, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 4, Box 57, Folder 1-2)
  - Thacher School, 2002-2005 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Home for the Aging Eisenberg Garden, 2002-2006 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - The Eli and Edythe Broad Stage (SMC Performing Arts Center Madison Theater), 2002-2007 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - CSUDH Loker Student Union, 2003-2008 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - UC Riverside Student Commons, 2003-2009 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Valley Regional High School #4, 2004-2011 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - CSUN Arbor Dining (Exchange Plaza), 2005-2007 (Box 58, Folder 4, Box 94, Folder 1)
  - CSUN Valley Performing Arts Center, 2006-2011 (Box 58, Folder 5, Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Chadwick School, 2007 (Box 58, Folder 6, Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Vista del Mar, 2007-2008 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Edison Language Academy SMMUSD, 2008-2014 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Fremont High School, 2009-2012 (Box 59, Folder 3, Box 94, Folder 4)
  - UCLA 16th Street Medical Center (Outpatient Surgery and Oncology), 2009-2013 (Box 59, Folder 4, Box 94, Folder 5)
  - UCSD Jacobs Medical Center Bed Tower, 2009-2017 (Box 59, Folder 5, Box 60, Folder 1-4, Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Kaiser Antelope Valley MOB, 2010-2011 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Laurence School, 2011-2012 (Box 61, Folder 2, Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - LA BioMed (Harbor UCLA Medical Center), 2012 (Box 61, Folder 3, Box 94, Folder 8)
  - UCI Merage School of Business, 2012 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Ofuna Housing, 2001-2007 (Box 61, Folder 5, Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Toyosu Housing Project, 2002-2004 (Box 61, Folder 6, Box 62, Folder 1-2, Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Ikonobe Cho Condos (Yokohama Housing), 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Chun Sen Bi An, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 4, Box 63, Folder 1, Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Glendale Sky Gardens, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Avenue of the Stars (The Century), 2005-2009 (Box 63, Folder 3-4, Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Century Hill, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 5, Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - 717 Ninth Street, 2006-2009 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - 301 Ocean Avenue, 2007-2008 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Stuyvesant Town/Peter Cooper Village, 2007-2008 (Box 64, Folder 3-4, Box 65, Folder 1-4, Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Tramonto, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Luxe Lake C3, 2010-2012 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Hipica Mixed-Use, 2011-2018 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Fresno Federal Courthouse, 1996-2006 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Contra Costa, 2000-2003 (Box 66, Folder 4-5)
  - Glendale Narrows Riverwalk, 2000-2003 (Box 66, Folder 6, Box 95, Folder 3)
  - DWP Santa Ynez Reservoir Water Quality Improvement, 2002-2004 (Box 67, Folder 1, Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Baldwin Hills Scenic Overlook, 2003-2007 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - National Palace Museum, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 3, Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - MWD Diemer, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - DWP Upper Stone Canyon Reservoir Water Quality Improvement, 2007-2008 (Box 67, Folder 5, Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Wallis Annenberg Performing Arts Center, 2007-2009 (Box 67, Folder 6, Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Santa Barbara Airport Terminal, 2007-2013 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Crescent Drive Parking Structure, 2008-2011 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Friesen Bonhill Residence, 1985-2012 (Box 68, Folder 4, Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Gyllenhaal Residence, 1992-2001 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Robyn Moore Residence, 1994-2002 (Box 68, Folder 6, Box 69, Folder 1, Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Chiate Residence, 1995-1998 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Crichton/Cantitoe Farm Residence, 1996-2002 (Box 69, Folder 3, Box 70, Folder 1-4, Box 71, Folder 1, Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Gibson-Wick Residence, 1997-1998 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Morton-Donnelley Residence, 1997-2001 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Gilbert Residence, 1997-2013 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Manson Residence, 1998-2002 (Box 71, Folder 5, Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Pfeiffer-Zohn Residence, 1998-2003 (Box 71, Folder 6, Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Brown La Mesa Residence, 1999-2008 (Box 72, Folder 1-2, Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Smalley-Wall Residence, 2000 (Box 72, Folder 3, Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Kiki Smith Residence, 2000-2001 (Box 72, Folder 4, Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Guggenheim Fields Marmont Residence, 2000-2002 (Box 73, Folder 1, Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Mountain Drive Trust Residence, 2000-2004 (Box 73, Folder 2-4, Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Lasker Residence, 2001 (Box 74, Folder 1, Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Morton Hamptons Residence, 2001 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Light Residence, 2001-2002 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Dvorak Residence, 2001-2003 (Box 74, Folder 4, Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Rothenberg Residence, 2001-2003 (Box 75, Folder 1-2, Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Bristol/Crichton Residence, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Morton Carolwood Residence, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 4, Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Harrison Residence, 2002-2004 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Moore Broad Beach House, 2002-2004 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Friesen Montecito Residence, 2002-2015 (Box 76, Folder 3-4, Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Chalon Residence, 2003 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Cohen Residence (Pelican Hill), 2003-2005 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Gilbert-Lurie (Ashley Ridge) Residence, 2003-2008 (Box 77, Folder 3-4)
  - Morton Beach House, 2003-2008 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Brown Beach House, 2003-2011 (Box 78, Folder 2, Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Alexander Residence, 2004 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Shilliday Residence, 2004 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Glean Residence, 2004-2005 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Ruscha Residence, 2004-2006 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Thacher Road (Steenburgen-Danson Ojai) Residence, 2004-2007 (Box 79, Folder 1-3, Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Englander Pond Residence (Happy Canyon), 2004-2008 (Box 79, Folder 4, Box 80, Folder 1, Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Wells Residence (Redtail Ranch), 2004-2008 (Box 80, Folder 2-3, Box 81, Folder 1, Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Crystal Residence, 2004-2011 (Box 81, Folder 2, Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Cordic Residence, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - East Fork (Bear Gulch) Residence, 2005-2008 (Box 81, Folder 4, Box 82, Folder 1-3, Box 97, Folder 8-9, Box 98, Folder 1-4)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Teviot Residence, 2005-2011 (Box 83, Folder 1-2, Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Rancho La Vista Residence, 2006-2007 (Box 83, Folder 3-4, Box 84, Folder 1-4, Box 98, Folder 6-7)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Lyon-Markowitz Residence, 2006-2008 (Box 85, Folder 1, Box 99)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Scenario Lane (Stone Canyon) Residence, 2006-2008 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Diamond-Davis Residence, 2006-2012 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Jusidman Residence, 2007 (Box 85, Folder 4, Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Tony Baldessari Residence, 2007-2011 (Box 86, Folder 1, Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Baldessari Residence, 2007-2012 (Box 86, Folder 2, Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Munitz (Lawenda) Residence, 2008 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Palladino Residence, 2008 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Donnelley Residence, 2008-2011 (Box 86, Folder 5, Box 99)
  - Hyde Residence, 2008-2011 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Rader Residence, 2008-2011 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Sanders Santa Ynez Residence, 2008-2012 (Box 87, Folder 2-3)
  - 960 Bel Air Road (Bay Residence), 2009-2010 (Box 87, Folder 4, Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Rosenblum Residence, 2009-2011 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Gerber Residence, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 2, Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Magnolia Barn Residence, 2010-2011 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Owen Residence, 2010-2011 (Box 88, Folder 4, Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Canada El Capitan Residence, 2011-2013 (Box 88, Folder 5, Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Lago Vista Drive Residence, 2011-2013 (Box 89, Folder 1-2, Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Hot Springs Road Residence, 2011-2015 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - 239 South El Medio Residence, 2012 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Solar Drive Residence, 2012 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Turbin Residence, 2012 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Howard Residence, 2012-2014 (Box 89, Folder 7-8)
  - Point Leo Residence, 2012-2014 (Box 90, Folder 1-4, Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Morton Stradella (Tintarella) Residence, 2012-2015 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Lorna Lane Residence, 2012-2016 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Project binders, 1992-2014; 15.1 Linear Feet (33 boxes); 0.8 Linear Feet (2 unprocessed boxes)
  These are binders used as administrative records for PB&Co projects. Each binder has printed information including: project directory, contacts, schedules, cost estimates, meeting notes, correspondence, and specifications. Some projects have only one binder, while others have several. The selected project binders in this archive range from projects beginning in the early 1990s through ones beginning in 2012.
  - Activision, 1997-2003 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
  - Aivazovskoje Resort (Black Sea), 2004 (Box 20, Folder 4-6)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Beckman Coulter, 2007-2010 (Box 21, Folder 1-5)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Cornerstone Sonoma Gallery, 2004-2005 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Lantana, 1996-2004 (Box 22, Folder 2-3)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - McMaster-Carr, 2003-2005; 2011-2014 (Box 22, Folder 4-6, Box 23, Folder 1-5, Box 24, Box 25, Folder 1-3)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Sony Capra, 2012 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Sony Rainbow, 2012 (Box 25, Folder 5, Box 26, Folder 1-2)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - FIDM Wilkinson, 2002-2004 (Box 26, Folder 3-5)
  - Brazil Esplanade, 2006-2009 (Box 27, Folder 1-4)
  - Civic Center Drive, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 1-3)
  - Palm Spiral, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
  - VIFX, 1997-2001 (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
  - IMAX Southern California Headquarters, 1998-2000 (Box 29, Folder 3-5, Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Farmers Market, 1996-2003 (Box 30, Folder 2-5, Box 31, Folder 1-4, Box 32, Folder 1-5)
  - Colorado Center (Yahoo), 2002-2004 (Box 33, Folder 1-5, Box 34, Box 35, Box 36, Box 37, Folder 1-6)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 106, Folder 6-8)
  - UCI Claire Trevor School of the Arts (SOTA) Arts Plaza, 2000-2005 (Box 38, Folder 1-5, Box 39, Box 40, Box 41, Box 42, Folder 1-4)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 106, Folder 9, Box 100, Folder 1)
  - SMUCLA Orthopaedic Medical Center, 1998-2012 (Box 42, Folder 5, Box 43, Folder 1-5, Box 44, Box 45, Box 46, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49, Folder 1-2)
    - Unprocessed oversize material (Box 100, Folder 2-3)
  - CSUN Valley Performing Arts Center, 2006-2011 (Box 49, Folder 3-4, Box 50, Folder 1)
  - CSUN Admin Building, 1999-2002 (Box 50, Folder 2-4, Box 51, Folder 1-2)
  - CSUN Masterplan, 1996-2000 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Valley Regional High School #4, 2004-2011 (Box 51, Folder 4-5)
  - Fremont High School, 2009-2012 (Box 52, Folder 1-2)
  - Scripps College Quotation Walk, 1992-1995; 2011 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Digitized project roll scans, 1970-2015; 855 Gigabytes (11,448 Files, 532 Folders); 1 Born-digital Carriers (1 hard drive) (Box 53)
  These files are scans of original project roll material of PB&Co projects that were digitized by PB&Co, and which span the entirety of Burton's career. Each project roll consists of any of the following: construction documents, architectural drawings, sketches, photographs, permits, surveys, and maps. Project rolls vary in size and scope. They range from the late 1970s through the mid-2010s. The older project rolls were drawn by hand and the newer project rolls were created using Computer Aided Design (CAD) software. As the PGB digital archive was being created, PB&Co selected and scanned material based on what they felt was representative of their landscape design.
  Arrangement
  The files are arranged according to project type: Commercial, Institutional, Residential, Large Scale Residential, Miscellaneous, Municipal. The files are further arranged according to project name.
  Please refer to the Digital File Naming Conventions pdf attached to this finding aid for a detailed explanation of the file directory hierarchy and structure of each Project Roll.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  CONTAINS DIGITAL MATERIALS: This collection contains processed digital materials. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.